Glory to "Shivaji Maharaja". Glory to "Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj"
When he chimed in, the clouds roared.
when he raised the sword, lightning strike.
Where he laid his feet,  Earth shakes.
Marathas had won by becoming death.
won all the "Forts" one by one.
Won all battles by battling with "antagonist".
on "Hind's" forehead  "Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj" is glowing like sun.
Shivaji Maharaj was a "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva"
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil) because of him.
He had keep the respect of Saffron flag.
Shivaji Maharaj was  "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva"
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil ) because of him.
He had keep the respect of Saffron flag.
He had sandalwood companion (a symbol of vitality).
Never consider religion-caste, always battled for soil (country).
went to fight, nobody's diplomacy worked.
He had waved the Saffron Flag (symbol of dharma) during "Mughal's reign".
'Father of Mughals'-Shivaji Maharaj
Aura like "sun"- Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj.
He had stood the 'self-Rule clan' by saying "har-har Mahadev".
You always have "Vijay Tilak" (symbol of victory).
My motherhood shield will protect you.
You have to protect this soil (country).
said by mother "Jija Bai" to Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj.
As long as you and your breathe remains, your enemy should have death in battle field.
fight till life lasts
stay country self respect.
Shivaji Maharaj was  "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva"
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil ) because of him.
He had keep the respect of Saffron flag.
Shivaji Maharaj was  "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva".
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil ) because of him.
He had kept the respect of Saffron flag.
Glory to "Shivaji Maharaja". Glory to "Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj"
He  taught "Lessons of bravery".
He made history.
He filled courage in everyone.
He  taught "Lessons of bravery".
He filled courage in everyone
every corner of "Shayadri" (a mountain).
Acclamation in all three loks (worlds).
Glory to mother " Bhavani". Glory to shivaji maharaj.
He tied country to the thread of Hind.
he wanted to colour the hind in  saffron.
He wanted to connect hind from all four sides.
He wanted that "Hind" should be standing like a mountain.
He offered his life to this reverved country.
He combat  a lot in battlefield.
He magicked on public.
Loose his life to wave the flag.
Shivaji Maharaj was  "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva".
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil ) because of him.
He  kept the respect of Saffron flag.
Shivaji Maharaj was  "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva".
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil) because of him.
He  kept the respect of Saffron flag.
Shivaji Maharaj was  "aura", "luster" and "sword".
He was aavtar (incarnation) of "Lord Shiva".
Earth is blessed and become red (means of blood of dead evil) because of him.
He  kept the respect of Saffron flag.
Heaps of dead bodies were increasing but  the blood never stopped shedding.
That lion Maratha kept fighting
, that Chhatrapati (King of Kings)  never bowed down