♪♪♪
[POWERFUL SHORT BIT]
[STEPS]
[BACKGROUND DIN]
[MANUAL WINDING]
[TURNING ON BIT]
[METALLIC CLICKY]
♪♪♪
♪ (LOOK OUT FOR YOURSELF) ♪
♪ I WAKE UP TO THE SOUNDS
OF THE SILENCE THAT ALLOWS ♪
♪ FOR MY MIND TO RUN AROUND,
WITH MY EAR UP TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ I'M SEARCHING TO BEHOLD ♪
♪ THE STORIES THAT ARE TOLD ♪
♪ WHEN MY BACK IS TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ THAT WAS SMILING WHEN
I TURNED ♪
♪ (TELL YOU YOU'RE
THE GREATEST) ♪
♪ (BUT ONCE YOU TURN
THEY HATE US) ♪
♪♪♪
♪ OH, THE MISERY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY ♪
♪ SPARE THE SYMPATHY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY-Y-Y-Y ♪
♪ [LOOK OUT FOR YOURSELF ♪
♪ MY ENEMY-Y-Y-Y ♪
♪ (LOOK OUT FOR YOURSELF) ♪
♪ BUT I'M READY ♪
♪ YOUR WORDS UP ON THE WALL ♪
♪ AS YOU'RE PRAYING
FOR MY FALL ♪
♪ AND THE LAUGHTER
IN THE HALLS ♪
♪ AND THE NAMES THAT I'VE BEEN
CALLED ♪
♪ I STACK IT IN MY MIND ♪
♪ AND I'M WAITING FOR THE TIME ♪
♪ WHEN I SHOW YOU WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE WORDS SPIT IN A MIC ♪
♪ (TELL YOU YOU'RE
THE GREATEST) ♪
♪ (BUT ONCE YOU TURN
THEY HATE US) ♪
♪♪♪
♪ OH, THE MISERY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY ♪
♪ SPARE THE SYMPATHY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY-Y-Y-Y ♪
♪ (LOOK OUT FOR YOURSELF) ♪
♪ MY ENEMY-Y-Y-Y ♪
♪ [JID] UH, LOOK, OKAY ♪
♪ I'M HOPING THAT SOMEBODY
PRAY FOR ME ♪
♪ I'M PRAYING THAT SOMEBODY
HOPE FOR ME ♪
♪ I'M STAYING WHERE
NOBODY 'POSED TO BE ♪
♪ P-P-POSTED ♪
♪ BEING A WRECK OF EMOTIONS ♪
♪ READY TO GO WHENEVER
JUST LET ME KNOW ♪
♪ THE ROAD IS LONG SO PUT
THE PEDAL INTO THE FLOOR ♪
♪ THE ENEMY'S ON MY TRAIL ♪
♪ MY ENERGY UNAVAILABLE ♪
♪ IMMA TELL 'EM HASTA LUEGO ♪
♪ THEY WANNA PLOT ON MY TROT
TO THE TOP ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN OUTTA SHAPE
THINKIN' OUT THE BOX
I'M AN ASTRONAUT ♪
♪ I BLASTED OFF THE PLANET ROCK
TO CAUSE CATASTROPHE AND IT
MATTERS ♪
♪ MORE BECAUSE I HAD IT NOT ♪
♪ HAD I THOUGHT ABOUT WREAKING
HAVOC ON AN OPPOSITION ♪
♪ KINDA SHOCKIN' THEY WANTED
STATIC ♪
♪ WITH PRECISION I'M AUTOMATIC
QUARTERBACK ♪
♪ I AIN'T TALKIN' SACKING
PACK IT PACK IT UP
I DON'T PANIC ♪
♪ BATTER BATTER UP
WHO THE BADDEST
IT DON'T MATTER ♪
♪ CAUSE WE AT YA THROAT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY ♪
♪ SPARE THE SYMPATHY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY ♪
♪ OH, THE MISERY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY ♪
♪ SPARE THE SYMPATHY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
MY ENEMY ♪
♪ PRAY IT AWAY, I SWEAR ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER BE A SAINT,
NO WAY ♪
♪ MY ENEMY ♪
♪ PRAY IT AWAY, I SWEAR,
I'LL NEVER BE A SAINT ♪
♪ LOOK OUT FOR YOURSELF ♪
[METALLIC CLICKY PLAYING
IN DISTANCE]